trust.com 2015-09-07

# Trust.com - Legal - Privacy Statement

Our support is organized by product. First you will need to find your product, then you will be able to get support, information, downloads, etc. 

The easiest way to find your product is to enter the 5-digit article number or (part of the) product name. The article number and name are both mentioned on the product itself and on the packaging. 

 Where can I find the article number? 

Your search has no results 

What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This policy covers how Trust treats personal information that Trust collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Trust services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Trust does not own or control, or to people that Trust does not employ or manage. Information

Collection and Use

  * Trust collects personal information (such as your name, e-mail address, gender and postcode) when you register with Trust, when you use Trust services and when you enter promotions or competitions.
  * Trust automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Trust cookie information, and the page you request.
  * Trust uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfil your requests for services, improve our services, contact you (when permitted or required), conduct research, and provide internal reporting.

Protection of personal data

  * Any information you submit will never be sold or passed to third parties or used for any other purpose, unless explicitly mentioned on the pages where the information is retrieved.
  * Personal information is requested to tune information to the needs of the user and to contact users when required.
  * While appropriate security measures are in place to ensure the protection of your personal data, Trust cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy policy. We have enlisted the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorised access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online.

E-mail policy

  * Trust uses opt-in with verification for user registration (e.g. at the Service Centre).
  * You will only receive e-mail from Trust mailing lists that you have subscribed to.
  * After registration at the Service Centre you will receive a confirmation e-mail. If you do not perform the actions requested in this e-mail (because e.g. you did not request the account), the account will automatically be deactivated.
  * After completing registration, filling in a contact form or requesting information on the website, you may receive e-mail to confirm reception of your request. This in no way implies subscription to any mailing list whatsoever.

Cookies

  * Cookies are little pieces of information, stored by the website on your computer. There are two types of cookies: session cookies, which your browser automatically deletes after leaving the site, and permanent cookies, which are not automatically deleted (but you can do that yourself).
  * Session cookies are used to enable certain types of services on the site. Disabling cookies may cause (parts of) the site to not work correctly. Session cookies are required for the Service Centre.
  * Permanent cookies are used to store user settings, like your preferred language.
  * No personal data is stored in cookies, unless explicitly accepted by you.

Google Analytics

  * This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computer’s hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy here for further information [<http://www.google.com/privacy.html>].
  * Trust make use of Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Trust may also make use of other Google Analytics for Display Advertising features, including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting and/or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. We are required by Google to disclose the following information to you in our Privacy Statement in connection with our use of any Google Analytics for Display Advertising features on Trust.Com: 
    * You may opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising or customize Google Display Network ads by using the [Google Ads Settings page.](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) You may also prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics by opting out through the use of the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).
    * If Trust make use of the Google Analytics for Display Advertising Remarketing feature, Trust will use such Remarketing feature to advertise online and third party vendors, including Google, may show Trust ads on sites across the Internet.
    * Trust and third party vendors, including Google, may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on a user's past visits to Trust, and/or (b) report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to Trust.Com.
    * Data from Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting may be utilized by Trust to help recognize and understand user preferences, to make improvements to Trust.Com, to choose content and advertising to display to you, and for other business purposes that will allow Trust to better serve you.

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

  * You can edit or delete your Trust-account at any time in the Service Centre. Login into the Service Centre and use the links under 'Your account'.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * Trust may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the e-mail address specified in your Trust-account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

Contact information

  * Trust values your opinion. If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please write to us at the following address:

Trust International BV  
Laan van Barcelona 600  
3317 DD Dordrecht  
The Netherlands
